Okay, so I am smelling fresh cake.
Now we've got a problem.
The problem is that recipe there is, um.
Okay.
Besides being incomplete, I think it's a chocolate cake recipe.
Yeah, okay.
But I've got a solution.
Yeah.
Do you know what it is?
No you don't.
Do you know what my solution is?
You've got an idea.
I'm going to show you the magic.
The magic?
How did you guess?
Okay, there we go.
Uh, YouTube.
Now you know how cool it would be to, like, have a video inside your page?
It's going to make it super awesome.
Yeah, and it's actually not that hard.
Yeah.
Now that you understand the basics of HTML, I'm going to show you how you can actually add a video.
So I've done a little Google or other little search here for making a carrot cake.
Uh, and I've come up with one very popular one, a million views.
So this one's got to be awesome.
So even if my chocolate cake recipe doesn't work for carrot cake, that's fine.
Uh, let's go and get a carrot cake.
So what we're now going to do, we want to embed her video.
You come here and you hit choose share.
And don't don't don't don't stress yourself.
Go down to where it says embed.
And here you are going to see C code.
There are actually a couple of things you can do.
Show player controls and all sorts of things that are going to be included in your bed option.
Show suggested videos.
You might say, okay, I don't want that afterwards.
I just want this video.
You can even start at a certain point if you like, but all you now need to do is grab that.
Now you recognize that.
What is that?
That's some code.
That's HTML code.
It's not that complex.
We haven't done the specific code exactly, but you will get the idea because all HTML code is similar.
So we're going to command C it and we're going to.
So we're going to come back here and just at the bottom here let's see what happens.
We're going to command V.
And we are going to just paste in that bit of code that we have just found.
It's actually an iframe piece of code, which means it's something that is going to be contained within
a frame.
Uh, but don't need to worry too much about that.
You just got to copy it and you'll see it's got the width and the height, and then it's got the source
of the video and what the frame border and whether to allow full screen or not.
So those are just some options.
But let's take a look.
So as simple as that, we run across to our best cake site and hit refresh.
And there's the video.
It has appeared on our page.
Now, obviously that's not exactly how we would like it.
We would maybe like it to be a little bit smaller and to fit here.
So the solution to that is just with this one we did we can, uh, you know, add in a whole bunch of
spaces.
And it has given this option to add the width and height.
Okay.
So now we just want to make it a little bit smaller than that.
So if we had to just change this 1 to 3 let's say 360 maybe 60.
What this is going to do is it's going to, it's going to make an image that looks like a square.
And we kind of want to keep it the same proportions.
So what we have here, proportional scaler I mean you can grab a calculator and work it out yourself.
So there's our original width and height.
And so if you just had that and you say resize it gives us it's going to be 2 or 2.5.
So if we just put an heart uh, so if you don't get the proportions right it's going to either make
it very long or very squishy or very weird.
Um, so, uh, so.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So now you can see it's, it's actually the right size.
It's.
Yeah.
So that, that, that looks now the right size.
But, uh, it still needs to be moved across.
Yeah.
So we're gonna just like we did with this one, we're going to have to add in a lot of spaces before
it.
So let's just grab this, grab some spaces.
We don't need that.
Let's just put that in right there.
Let's just try that one save.
We'll put refresh this and are nearly there I'd say just a few more.
Uh, let's just ah, you're two shakes of a a small dog's tail.
Oh my God, he's gobsmacked.
Okay, so let's just.
Save that.
So.
Let's say that's enough.
Let's try that.
It's all in the fine tuning okay.
Oh, so close, so close, so close.
I think you're going to need, like, one more.
One more.
I think it's two more.
No, no, because it's a whole bunch.
Yeah.
Let's see.
And I told you.
I told you that's one.
Yeah.
That's a that's it's perfect.
It's perfect.
You've hit it.
And that's looking really good.
I mean, we could sit here and fiddle but you get the idea.
So here we've got our sights actually looking pretty cool.
We've got our recipe, we've got our little image, we've got our video.
And now you'll see if you hit play.
This video is going to now be playing our best ever carrot cake.
Best ever carrot cake.
How to make it so it's all happening here on your side.
And you've actually made this whole thing.
I mean it's pretty impressive.
It's all embedded in your site.
So there we go.
Go along.
Embed a video in your site.
We showed you how to do it.
You just simply grab the embed code and you come across insert it on your site.
Remember you may need to just change the the width and the height proportionately.
Add a few little spaces in and you are ready to rock and roll.
So only one thing left, and that is to link this page with that page.
And you've then got a complete website.
So over to you.
We're nearly there and you're doing fantastic.